Do you believe that your dreams are your own?
Strawberry Mansion is a fantasy, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Kentucker Audley.
In the not-too-distant future, an all-seeing surveillance state conducts “dream
audits” to collect taxes on the unconscious lives of the populace.
Mild-mannered government agent James Preble travels to a remote farmhouse to audit
the dreams of Arabella “Bella” Isadora, an eccentric, aging artist.
Entering Bella’s vast VHS archive, which contains a lifetime of dreams, Preble
stumbles upon a secret that offers him a chance at love—and hope for escape.
Arabella “Bella” Isadora, played by Penny Fuller.
James Preble, played by Kentucker Audley.
Young Bella, played by Grace Glowicki.
Peter Bloom, played by Reed Birney.
Buddy, played by Linas Phillips.
Martha, played by Constance Shulman.
Strawberry Mansion is a 2021 American surrealist science fantasy adventure
film directed and written by Albert Birney and Kentucker Audley.
It stars Penny Fuller, Kentucker Audley, Grace Glowicki, Reed
Birney, Linas Phillips
and Constance Shulman.
The tone is thought_provoking.